https://tonerrefillkits.com/privacy/

9am - 5pm
M - F (ET)
TonerRefillKits.com THE Toner Experts Since 1987
( )
9am - 5pm
M - F (ET)
Our Commitments to You
We do not sell information to third parties.
We do not and will not share your information to any outside parties who may wish to market their products to our customers.
Customers do not have to take any action or instruct us to keep their information confidential.
This page describes the privacy practices for www.TonerRefillKits.com and includes:
Personally Identifyable Information Collection and Use
The categories of information are: transactional information, relational information and website usage or statistics. TonerRefillKits.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. TonerRefillKits.com collects information from our users at several different points on our Website.
TonerRefillKits.com complies with state laws regarding privacy including the California Online Privacy Protection Act, effective July 1, 2004.
Forms for Ordering or RegistrationsOur site's forms require customers to give us contact information such as name, email address and customer information for ordering and shipping our products. Purchases using credit cards require information to complete the transaction including credit card numbers, expiration dates, and other codes required by merchant clearing services. See "Privacy" below for more information.
Transactional or Relationship MessagesNew customers who purchase products from us will receive e-mail messages and a newsletter from us. Established customers will occasionally receive information on products, special promotions, and a newsletter. Messages are used communicate information including but not limited to order status, confirmations, shipping or tracking information, promotions, newsletters, surveys, and other information to our customers. Customers who wish to not receive communications from TonerRefillKits.com can use our opt-out/unsubscribe links. The preferred method of unsubscribing is to use the links in the communications. You can also unsubscribe to any message by sending a note to [email protected] with REMOVE in the subject line.
Permission MarketingTonerRefillKits.com complies with the CAN-SPAM act of 2003, effective January 1, 2004. TonerRefillKits respects the privacy of individuals and businesses and does not condone or participate in SPAM mailings. From time to time, TonerRefillKits.com may send email messages to people who may be interested in our products through the use of opt-in mailing lists. We only use lists from vendors who certify that the list was obtained from opt-in sources. Whenever possible, we will identify the list where the opt-in name was obtained in the header of our email message. If you believe that you have received such a message in error, please follow the directions in the email message to unsubscribe or remove yourself from the list. In any case, you can always send an email to [email protected] for changes. SurveysAny voluntary feedback information provided is used TonerRefillKits.com to understand and respond to our customer requirements, concerns, and better enable us to meet their needs. This information is never shared with anyone outside our company. From time to time, we will ask customers and visitors to the site to participate in voluntary surveys to help us further enhance our service. These surveys are important to us but are entirely voluntary.
Referral Programs / Forward to a FriendIf a customer elects to use our referral programs to inform a friend about our products, we ask you to enter email addresses of friends who may want to know about our products and services. TonerRefillKits.com stores this information for the sole purpose of sending email communications including a one-time email inviting them to view our site and see the products we offer. Occasionally, we will send information on products, special offers, and a newsletter to referral email addresses. To unsubscribe, follow the instructions in the email message.
SecurityWe use industry-standard technology to keep your personal information as secure as possible. Our Website takes precautions to protect our customers' information. We use secure technology and protection controls to safeguard your personal information. When customers submit sensitive information via the website, the information is protected both online and off-line.
When our order form asks customers to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with industry-standard encryption SSL (secure socket layer) software. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers becomes locked to show the session is secure as opposed to un-locked, or open. We use third-party verification services for credit card authorization. TonerRefillKits.com does not store any credit card information on our website but passes the credit card information to our third-party clearning house via SSL encryption. Your information is also used internally in our in-house systems to allow us to charge your credit card when your order is shipped. We do get an authorization from the merchant services when your order is placed and then when your order is shipped, we "capture" the funds. This ensures that you won't be charged for anything unless we are shipping that item to you.
We protect the confidentiality of Customer Information. TonerRefillKits.com does not share or release customer information. TonerRefillKits.com will never willfully disclose personal information about our customers nor email addresses nor contact names to any outside parties without receiving written permission or unless ordered to do so by a court of law.
If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email [email protected]
Service ProvidersWe partner with other third parties to provide specific services such as credit card clearning, site statistics or visitor tracking, newsletters, email notifications, and promotions or our shopping cart services). When you utlilze these services, we share names, or other contact information (email address, organization) necessary for the third party to provide these services. We only share information to complete the transaction or to complete a relational communication. These third parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services to us. Each third party has security policies to protect confidential information.
How To Make Changes By Updating or Correcting Your InformationIf a customer's information changes (such as your email address or title), we will provide a way to update that customer's information. TonerRefillKits.com customers may contact:[email protected] with any changes.
Opt-out/UnsubscribeCustomers who no longer wish to receive online communications or specific items from us may opt-out or unsubscribe from receiving these communications. Each communication will have a way to unsubscribe from that list. Please carefully follow the instructions on the communication to ensure removal of your name from our lists. If you encounter any difficulty, please email us at:[email protected]
Links to Other SitesThis web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that TonerRefillKits.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or security of such other sites. We encourage our customers to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by http://www.TonerRefillKits.com.
Website Usage: CookiesA cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. We may use cookies to save information (name, address, phone number, email address) so you don't have to re-enter them each time you visit our site. We also use cookies to allow you to easily log in to your optional account. If you have chosen to disable cookies, you can still use our service, but you may be required to fill in information each time you sign on.
Website Statistics: Log FilesWe use IP addresses to analyze overall trends for our web site(s), administer our sites, help diagnose problems with our servers, track customer's movements, monitor and protect against fradulent use of our site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use, We may from time-to-time aggregate our users' system information and share that with partners (whom are under confidentiality obligations), but in no case is an individual's specific system configuration revealed to third parties. We track visits through our site to enable us to analyze aggregate information to help us understand our customer's and prospects paths through our site and pages visited.
Website: Live Help (Chat feature)Our website features an optional live chat feature to allow customers to get sales support and ordering help during business hours. The chat identifies the computer's IP address and tracks session information. If you do not wish to utilize this feature, do not click on the Live Help button.
How We Notify You of Changes to Our PolicyIf we decide to change any of the terms of our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our website so customers are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify customers by way of an email. Customers will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
Brother
Canon
Dell
Hewlett Packard / HP
Lexmark
ReChargX
Samsung
Xerox
Can't Find Your Model?
Help
Newsletter
Sign Up for Our Newsletter:
Submit
© 1987 - 2020 TonerRefillKits.Com. All Rights Reserved. ReChargX®, TonerRefillKits.com® and designs are U.S. registered trademarks
